<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AI Story Teller</string>
    <string name="grocery_list_desc">AI Based App For Kids</string>
    <string name="app_dummy">"This is the Rapunzel and Tangled Story. Once upon a time, a long time ago, deep in a forest lived an evil witch. Gothel, the evil witch had a magical flower, that helped her hide her true age. This flower had great healing flowers. Now, not far from the forest was a kingdom. The queen of the kingdom had been expecting a child for a long. But due to certain unexpected complexities, she had endangered her own life as well as of the unborn child. Now, in search of something to save the queen’s life and the unborn child, the soldiers found the flower Gothel had in her garden. The flower was given to the queen and the queen quickly recovered. And soon a beautiful baby princess was welcomed. While celebrations enveloped the kingdom, Gothel, the evil witch cried in agony upon finding her flower being stolen. But soon, she heard that the daughter of the king held the same powers as the flower. It was the hair of the princess to be exact. She also came to know that if the hair was cut off the golden hair turned black and lost powers. So, alone she hatched a plan and implemented it too. She sneaked into the castle and stole the princess away in the dead of the night. The poor infant of a princess was taken away to a high-walled tower, that was Gothel’s home and locked in the highest room. “She shall stay here, and help me disguise my age, forever and evermore!” The poor princess grew in the castle tower not knowing who she truly was until she met with an intruder and had an adventure. Flynn Rider, a well-known bandit enters Rapunzel’s castle in search of something to steal. But he had not anticipated that he would be knocked out and captured! When he woke, he found a girl with long beautiful golden locks staring at him. “Who are you? Why are you here?” Now, Flynn Rider has run away from the kingdom after stealing the Rapunzel’s crown. But before Flynn could say something, Rapunzel begins searching for his things and discovers the crown. Unaware that it was her very own crown she cracks a deal with the thief. Hiding the crown she says, “You shall take me to see the "</string>

</resources>